[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 11, "question": "And was the truth a victim, too?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 12, "answer": "They're 100 percent innocent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "She was the only person you saw?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Pretty much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "Did you have a television?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "There was a television, no cable anything like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "What was the bed like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "It's a concrete slab along the back of the wall.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "A computer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "CHOLS: No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Were you following them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Just what I would see on, like, the major network television stations.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "How often were you allowed to exercise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "As often as you do it yourself in your cell.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "When did you see daylight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "In 10 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "For almost 10 years, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "I mean, this is -- for an innocent man, as many believe that you are and you've always protested this -- what are you thinking when you're stuck in there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "The only thing -- the only thing you can do and maintain your sanity is to not think about the case and not think about what's happening to you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "What effect did it have on your health?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "My health -- there's almost no medical care, no dental care, and things like that in prison so my health was deteriorating very rapidly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Yes, but that first moment you came out, what was it like to have daylight again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "It was like having a spotlight turned right in your face.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "They don't give you forks in there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "How do you eat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "With your hands.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "When is the first time that you hear you are going to be in trouble with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Almost immediately, and it wasn't just because of this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RBS", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Or were you just a bit different?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "The most trouble I had ever gotten into was like running away from home as a teenager, something like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Ever broken the law?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "You were into, like, heavy metal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "IN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "So what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Just immediately, as soon as it happened, people said a murder this horrific couldn't have just happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "When was the moment you realized you were going to be pulled in by the police?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "They showed up at my door the day after the bodies were found.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "And how did that make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "There's no words to even describe it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "What happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Well, whenever they called him in for questioning, like you said, he was mentally retarded.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "How well did you know him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Not very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Why did you think he was doing this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "It's hard to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "When is the worst moment for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "It's hard to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "What was the evidence against you, other than the word of Jessie, who we already established had a mental age of somewhere between a 5 and 8- year-olds?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "The evidence against us was our personal preferences in music.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jessie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 242, "question": "There's no DNA evidence against you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Well, at the time they had evidence and stuff but since it didn't match us it wasn't brought up and then --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Was there anything else other than music you listened to, books you read, clothes you wore or haircuts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ",", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "That was it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "And they would attack you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "How often?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "The first few years, a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBD", "RP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Like what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "I mean I've got shattered skull, broken collarbone, teeth knocked out, multiple scars on my face and stuff from it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "I mean were you going through the same thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lorri"]}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "You write about -- what are you thinking when these letters arrive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "I think I fell in love with Lorri pretty much from the very first letter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Because I can -- I just knew this was someone unlike anyone I had ever known in my life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "VBN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "But you must have still had family, friends, and people around you, presumably, as this relationship developed, thinking, what are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBD", "RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Well, fortunately, for most of my life I've been a pretty grounded, responsible person so I mean I think if I had been a little more erratic in my life, then maybe -- but it was astounding because my close friends stuck by me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "How -- you know, how do you deal with that psychologically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "I never entertained the thought of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "But if you didn't take this deal, he would have been facing the death penalty still, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Well, on both deals, like they came to me with plea agreements, like, when I first got arrested.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "How many execution dates did you face?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "I only ever had one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "And in the build-up to that, did you genuinely think that you were going to get killed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "DT", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "I thought there was a good possibility, just because -- you know, we were convicted of something we didn't do with no evidence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "How many people were on Death Row with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "It varies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Any of them believe you may be guilty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "None of mine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "None of yours?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Well, the thing about that is I was with my family at the time the murders occurred.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Jason, why do you think Jessie was doing this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jessie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Because if he hadn't, I don't think any of you would have gone to prison, would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "The closest thing I can come to explain that in my mind is like the schoolyard bully who gets the kid to cry uncle under duress.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Do you blame him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "He's a victim as well, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "How do you deal with that psychologically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "You just have to keep moving forward.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Was it, yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "We were terrified for his safety, you know, when we first heard of the murders.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Does a part of you understand why some of their family felt they had closure with your convictions?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "CHOLS: Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "And they just can't deal with the fact that it may not be what they had been told it was?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Absolutely, I can understand it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "When you saw him described as this evil ring leader of mass murder, what were you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "I knew everybody just had it wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Did either of you ever have suicidal thoughts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "But not after you were put in prison?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Did you ever try to take your own life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Yeah, I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "How?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "I took an overdose of basically sleeping pills, anti- depressants, just because it was -- like you said a while ago, there's no light at the end of the tunnel.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "That moment when you walk free, how did that feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "It's hard to describe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Lorri, were you surprised at the strength of Damien through this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lorri", "Damien"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Did you see him at all during the time you were inside?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Not very often of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "How does he deal with what's happened to his father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "Did you believe in it before this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "I didn't give it much thought.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "You did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "I would stop it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "What are the practical realities of your life now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "I am -- I sleep very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Had your first beer yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Quite a few I should say, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "I think, at one point, I went to a coffee shop and they were like what kind of coffee do you want.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "What's it been like for you, Damien?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "I think one of the most remarkable moments that let me know that it was really finally over is we had friend who took us to see like an improv comedy routine.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Damien"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "And that was the fear you lived with for ten years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "Every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Have you managed to get work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "Not yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "You've only been out, what, six weeks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RP", ",", "WP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "A month -- a month and a week.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Who decides that, the governor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "The governor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "Governor of Arkansas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Arkansas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "RB", ",", "CC", "NN", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "Is there a petition to him at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "I don't think it's been put together yet, but everybody's been talking about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "Is the case still open or was it closed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "To the prosecutors, it's closed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Should it be reopened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110929pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "That's when everybody -- right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "In that sense, that's what we have been working on all these years with the legal team and people who have helped us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]